剧情回顾...
previously on "lost"...
我不知道是为什么...
I don't know how it happened,
你和这座岛有某种联系 John
but you seem to have some communion with this island,John
这让你变得特别重要
and that makes you very,very important.
到时候你就会明白的
In time, you'll have a better understanding of things.
Kwon怀孕了
Kwon is pregnant.
胎儿很健康
The fetus is healthy--
-那是什么?     -Juliet在你们的营地里搜集情报
-what's that?  -Juliet is gathering information for us at your former camp.
如果谁怀孕了
She's determining if any of the women are pregnant.
我们会过去带走他们
Then we're gonna go in and... take them.
Juliet是个内奸 她在为Ben做事
Juliet is a mole.She's working for ben.
-我们要走了    -走?去哪儿?
-We're moving. -Moving? Where are we going?
我们哪里都不去 John
We are not going anywhere,John.
你要留在这里
You are going to stay behind.
我们给你留下了踪迹 让你能跟上
We'll leave a trail--one you can track.
John 除非你背上...
And,John,unless you're carrying
你父亲的尸体...
your father's body on your back...
否则别来打扰我们
don't bother.
加油  用力啊!
come on! Damn it, push!
有些不对劲  我不能...
something's wrong.I can't...
Emily
你能做到的 现在你要用力!
You can do this! Now push!
你能行的  宝贝  坚持住!
Come on. Come on, baby.You can do it. Now come on.
坚持住!
come on.
就是这样  坚持住!
There you go! Come on!
是个男孩
It's a boy.
你做到了
You did it.
好痛啊!
It hurts.
你做到了
oh, you did it.
Roger我好痛啊!
Roger, it hurts.
Emily没人知道我们在这里
Emily, no one knows we're out here.
我们必须回去  好吗  亲爱的?
We gotta get back,okay, honey?
你能抱住他吗?
Can you hold on to the baby?
Emily你能抱住宝宝吗?
Emily, can you hold the baby?
抱紧了
Hold him tight.
救命啊!
hey!Help! Help!
Help!
救命啊!
快  来帮帮我
Come on. Help me.
怎么了  老兄?
Hey, what happened, man?
我们在徒步旅行 她早产了
We were hiking.She went into labor,and she wasn't due yet.
她还在流血
She's bleeding.
-我们把她弄到车上去  好吗?    -好
-We'll put her in the car,okay?   -Okay.
我们会把你送到医院去的
We're gonna get you to the hospital.
好了  好了宝贝
oh, okay. Okay, honey.
我们别让他着凉了
okay,it's all right.Let's keep her warm. All right?
-宝宝怎么样了?     -他没问题  我也不知道
-How's the baby?   -Fine, I guess. I don't know.
Roger...
-Roger...  -我就在这里
-roger...  -I'm right here.
叫他Benjamin...
Call him benjamin...
坚持住!
stay with me.
坚持住啊Emily!
Stay with me. Emily!
Emily!天啊  不!
Emily! Oh, God, no!
那是什么?
what you got there?
生日礼物
It's a birthday present.
今天是我的生日
Mine just happens to be today.
你该记得生日吧 Richard?
You do remember birthdays,don't you, Richard?
想让我把磁带交还给Juliet吗?
So do you want me to bring the, uh, tape back to Juliet?
什么?
What?
那盘有你指示Juliet计划的磁带...
The tape with your instructions for Juliet--
想要我带回医疗站吗?
do you want me to bring it back to the medical station?
我昨天才录的 在我们走之前
I recorded it yesterday before we left.
-我以为你已经拿走了     -没有
-I thought you already took it.   -No.
Tom在哪里?
Where's tom?
Tom!
看见我的录音机了吗?
Have you seen my recorder?
你答应我 如果我杀了我父亲
You said that if I killed my father,
你就会告诉我这座岛的一切
you'd tell me everything I wanted to know about the island.
不如从开头说起吧?
so why don't you start at the beginning?
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www.YYETS.com
■
翻译：   许愿  后期：梁良 双语字幕：七色九天
我是答应过你 John
I know I promised to tell you everything,John,
翻开一本旧书那么简单
me taking out a dusty old book and opening it up.
但没那么简单
But it's not that simple.
不如你来告诉我
How about you just tell me?
你或许认为
You probably think
我是这个社区的领导
I'm the leader of this little community,
但这不完全正确
but that's not entirely true.
我们都得听一个人的 John
We all answer to someone,John.
那么这个人是谁呢?
And who might that be?
他叫Jacob
His name is Jacob.
那好 带我去见Jacob
Okay, then.Take me to Jacob.
我做不到
I can't do that.
-你去哪儿?    -Ben 如果你不愿意带我去
-Where are you going?  -Hell,Ben,if you don't want to take me,
也许其他人愿意  我会去问Richard
maybe someone else will. I'll just go and ask Richard.
Richard为什么会带你去?  他根本不知道Jacob在哪里
Why would richard take you? He doesn't know where Jacob is.
-他不和Jacob说话       -那谁才和他说话?
-He doesn't talk to Jacob.   -Well, who talks to him?
-我啊   -就你一个人吗?
-I do.  -Oh,you're the only one who talks to him?
-当然    -其他人都不知道他在哪儿?
-That's right.  -And no one else knows where he is?
我出生在这座岛上
I was born here on this island.
我在这里最有资格
I'm one of the last that was.
你看见的大多数人 都是我带来的
Most of these people you see--I brought them here,
Jacob只跟我说话 John
so Jacob talks to me,John.
他告诉我该做什么
He tells me what to do,
他信任我
trusts me.
没有人见过他吗?
And no one else has ever seen him?
没错
That's right.
多方便啊
How convenient.
你知道我怎么想吗 Ben?
You know what I think,Ben?
我想根本就没什么Jacob
I think there is no Jacob.
你们的人都是白痴
I think your people are idiots
如果他们相信你从某人那里得到命令
if they believe you take orders from someone else.
你就是那个在幕后指使的人
You are the man behind the curtain...
就像绿野仙踪...
the wizard of oz...
你是个骗子
and you're a liar.
你凭什么这么说 John?
And what might you base that theory on, John?
因为如果你说的是实话
Because if you were telling the truth,
你的手就不会抖了
your hand wouldn't be shaking.
你好
Namaste
谢谢
Thanks
你好
namaste
欢迎来这岛上  老兄
Hey,welcome to the island, man.
你好
Namaste.
你认为怎么样?
So what do you think?
这真是个好地方
Wow, this is some place.
谢谢你给我这个机会 Goodspeed先生
Thanks again for the opportunity, Mr.Goodspeed.
请叫我Horace
Horace, please.
-Horace   -这一定是Ben咯
-Horace.  -And this must be Ben.
你出生的时候 Goodspeed先生就在你身边
Mr. Goodspeed was there the day you were born.
是啊
Yes, I was.
他帮了我们一个大忙 给了你老子一个工作
He's doing us a big favor here. He gave your old man a job.
他不怎么说话
Uh,he don't say much.
没关系的  有话说的时候他会说的
That's okay. I bet he will when he has something to say,
对吗 Ben?
right,Ben?
你饿了吗  孩子?
Hey, you hungry, kiddo?Huh?
很好  我告诉你吧
Great. All right,well, I tell you what.
等你们都弄好了 我们准备了午餐
After you're done processing,we'll have some lunch.
-这样如何?   -谢谢
-How's that sound?  -Uh,thank you.
你一定会爱上这里的
You're gonna love it here.
欢迎来岛上
Welcome to the island.
为了你们自己的安全
For your own comfort and safety,
你们必须待在住宅区
we ask that you stay within the confines
的界限内
of your new living quarters.
我们的社区被...
Our barracks are surrounded
高频率的声纳防御系统...
by a high-frequency sonar fence
保护着
to protect us
为了防范岛上各类野生动物
from the island's abundant and diverse wildlife.
现在你就是达摩组织的一员了
you are now a member of the Dharma Initiative.
是什么野生动物
What kind of wildlife you think
要我们这样防御?
this fence is protecting us from?
-Roger Linus? Roger Linus?   -是我
-Roger Linus? Roger Linus.   -Yeah.
每天早上你都会得到一组新的密码
Every morning you will be given a new code
来越过这道防御系统
which will allow you to cross outside the fences if you so desire.
这座岛上有
There are properties on this island
地球上其它地方都没有的特性
that exist nowhere else on earth.
我们的任务就是 研究这些特性
Our mission is to study these properties
为了人类能更好的生存
for the betterment of mankind
增进世界的和平
and advancement of world peace.
大部分的人会在岛的主要地区工作
Most of you will be working on the mainland.
如果你被分配去地质研究...
Should you be assigned geological study...
你是新来的吧?
Hey. You're new, huh?
我叫Annie
I'm Annie.
要一块吗?
Want one?
想要多少就有多少
We can have as many as we want.
"工人"?
"Work man"?
这是什么?  工人?
What is this? Work man?
我只是个当工的?
I'm a janitor?
-很抱歉Linus先生   -Goodspeed告诉我你们在做什么实验
-I'm sorry, Mr.Linus.  -Goodspeed told me you people were doing experiments,
改变世界
changing the world.
我可不是来打杂的
I didn't come here to clean up after you.
如果工作有空闲
Look,if anything else opens up,
你随时都可以来申请
you can feel free to apply for it.
我们走
come on.
Hey,Sayid
你怎么了?
What happened to you?
-我和Locke在一起    -那他人呢?
-I was with Locke.  -Well,where is he?
他又回去了
He went back.
-回去哪里?    -和他们   别问我在哪里
-Back where?  -With them.Don't ask me where the hell it is,
因为现在说这个并不重要
'cause it doesn't matter right now.
真正重要的  是这个
What does matter... is this.
Ben在哪里?!
Where is Ben?!
他在哪里?!
Where is he?!
我以为你已经死了
I thought you were dead.
幸运的是高压电塔 没调到致命的级别
I'm fortunate the pylons were not set to a lethal level.
他在这里做什么?
What is he doing here?
他想杀了我
He's the one who tried to kill me.
他和我们是一伙的了
He's with us now.
你去哪里了 Mikhail?
Where have you been,Mikhail?
我遇见了他们的几个人
I encountered several of his people in the jungle.
还有一个受伤的女人
They had an injured woman with them.
很显然  她刚降落到这座岛上
Apparently,she had just parachuted onto the island.
-什么?  -她的直升机坠毁在了海里
-What?  -Her helo crashed in the water.
她说她的船就在朝西
She says her ship is approximately 130 clicks
130公里外
to the west of us.
-她有个卫星无线电    -她在哪儿?
-She has a radio-telephone. -Where is she now?
我猜是被他们带回营地了
I assume they have taken her back to their camp.
我们后天会造访他们的营地
We'll be visiting their camp day after tomorrow.
-到时会处理这件事的      -后天?  我们必须现在行动
-We'll take care of it then.    -Day after tomorrow? We have to go now.
-Ben不会和你去任何地方的    -你说什么?
-Ben's not going anywhere with you.  -Excuse me?
他和我要去见Jacob
He and I are going to see Jacob.
告诉我他说的不是实话 Benjamin
Please tell me this isn't true,Benjamin.
抱歉  我必须先处理这件事 John
Sorry. I have to deal with this now, John.
我们的旅行只能延后了
Our excursion will have to wait.
什么时候开始你要向他做出解释 一个外来者?
Since when do you explain yourself to him--an outsider?
Tom
Richard?!
我们什么时候出发?
so when do we leave?
你不用毫无道理的揍Mikhail
you know, you didn't have to beat Mikhail senseless
来表示你的想法 John
to make your point, John.
不  我用的着
Yes, I did.
Locke...
我听说你要去见Jacob
I hear you're gonna go see Jacob.
你需要这个
You're gonna need this.
谢谢
Thanks.
生日快乐  爸爸
Happy birthday, dad.
当水加入了小苏打里
so once water is added to the bicarbonate,
我们的火山就会爆发了
we will get our very own volcanic reaction.
是的
Yes.
这里的火山也这样吗?
Is that what happened to the volcano on this island?
完全正确 Annie  不过那还是在很久以前了
Exactly,Annie,but that was a long time ago.
好了  我们来实践一下
Okay,let's get ourselves an eruption.
太棒了!
oh,cool!
只要加入水
Just add water,and voil.
我知道这不是喷发...
Now I know it's not lava,but--
那是什么?!
what was that?!
不  他们来了
oh no they're coming
大家各就各位
okay,everyone,into your positions.
大家都趴下 快点!
Everyone,get down! Hurry!
到这边来!
Get over here!
对了  待在一块儿
That's right,all together.
Annie 请你把门锁了
Annie,lock the back door,please.
快点!
Ben,come on,honey,
快行动起来 Ben!
you gotta move.Ben!
来啊
come on!
别担心  只是"敌人们"
don't worry. It's just the hostiles.
我们会没事的
We'll be okay.
趴下!
get down!
老兄  听说你遇到麻烦了
hey,man,I heard you ran into a little trouble.
我们从飞机那儿往回赶
we were driving back from the plane,
听见了巨大的爆炸声
and we hear this huge explosion.
警笛响个不停
Next thing I know,there's a siren wailing,
我们从枪林弹雨中回来了
and we're driving through the middle of a shootout.
我们和当地人有些冲突
Look,we're having some skirmishes with the natives.
你什么意思  当地人?
What do you mean,natives?
我们还不确定他们到底是什么人
Well,we're not exactly sure who they are.
我不是为了这个来的
Well,this ain't what I signed up for.
Roger 我帮助过你
Roger,I did you a favor,man.
你自己找不到工作
You were having trouble finding work,
别忘了Ben 他在这里接受良好的教育
and don't forget about Ben. He's getting a quality education.
我对他的教育不感兴趣
I don't give a damn about his education.
如果我被射中了 我需要保险
If I'm gonna get shot at,I want hazard pay.
-我要另外30000    -冷静点  老兄
-I want another 30 grand.  -Calm down,man.
别告诉我你没有
and don't try to tell me you don't have it.
你听见了吗?  从我家滚出去
You hear me? Now get the hell out of my house.
我告诉过你早点睡觉
I thought I told you to go to bed.
她不在这里
She's not here.
早就知道
I noticed.
你们在做什么?
What are you doing?
在找Juliet
Looking for Juliet.
你们在这里找不到她
Well,you're not gonna find her in there.
-她和Jack一起走了     -Juliet和Jack吗?
-She left with jack.  -Juliet left with Jack?
在我告诉他关于Naomi的事后他就走了
He took off right after I told him about Naomi.
谁是Naomi?
Who's Naomi?
你为什么要这么做 Kate?
And why would you do that,kate?
因为她受伤了 而他又是个医生
Because she's hurt,because he's a doctor
因为他有权知道
and because he has a right to know.
他现在在哪里?
Where is he now?
-我不知道 Sayid      -你当然不知道
-I don't know,sayid. -Of course you don't.
是时候告诉大家Naomi的事了
It might be time for you to tell everybody else about Naomi,too.
给她放磁带
Play her the tape.
什么磁带?
What tape?
在走之前我要告诉你 John
There's something you should know,John,before we go.
不管你认为他是Oz的巫师(绿野仙踪)还是别的什么
Whether or not you think he's the wizard of oz,
我能保证Jacob是一个非常真实的人
I can assure you that Jacob is very,very real.
我们要去见他
And we're gonna go see him,
他会很不开心的
and he's not gonna like it.
我想他会非常生气的
In fact,I have a feeling he's gonna be very...angry.
那就是我手抖的原因
And that's why my hand was shaking,
因为那个人不是你能造访的
because this is not a man you go and see.
是他召唤你
This is a man who summons you.
凡事总有第一次嘛!
Well,I guess there's a first time for everything.
这是我们
It's us.
那个是你 这个是我
That's you,and that's me.
我们会永远在一起了
Now we never have to be away from each other.
生日快乐 Ben
Happy birthday,Ben.
谢谢
Thanks.
别客气
You're welcome.
今天是你生日
it's your birthday.
抱歉我忘了
Sorry I forgot.
在你把你妈杀了的这天
It's kinda hard to celebrate
庆祝恐怕有些困难
on the day you killed your mom.
她怀孕才7个月
She was just seven months pregnant.
我们去徒步旅行
We went for a hike,
没想到早产了
but you had to come early.
现在她死了...
Now she's gone...
而我只能和你困在这座岛上
and I'm stuck here on this island...with you.
生日快乐 Ben
happy birthday,Ben.
妈妈?
mom?
Ben不要
Ben,don't!
妈妈!
Mom!
现在还不是时候 Benjamin
It's not time yet,Benjamin.
妈妈!
Mom!
我们走 John
Let's go,John.
John
整个世界都认为我们死了?
So,what,the whole world thinks we're dead?
-现在这个并不重要   -不重要吗?
-That's not important right now.   -Not important?
-什么才是重要的Sayid?  -抱歉
What do you mean,it's not important,sayid?  -excuse me.
我很抱歉  你们不想得救吗?
I'm sorry.  Don't you people want to be rescued?
我们为她保密来保证我们的安全
We kept her a secret to keep her safe.
为了什么 Sayid?
Safe from what,Sayid?
为了Jack 他和"the others"一起待了一周
Safe from Jack. He spent a week with the others,
还带了一个他们的人回来
and he brought one of them back with him,
在这里  我们当中
here,amongst us,
每次我们去问这个女人的时候
and every time we try to get answers from this woman,
他总会去保护她
he prevents her from giving them.
但他是Jack啊
But it's jack.
他永远不会做伤害我们的事
He would never do anything to hurt us.
-还有Juliet  我相信她是个好人   -好人咯?
-And Juliet... I believe she's a good person.  -Good person,huh?
你凭什么这样认为? 不会就是因为她带你...
You're base in that on what? Wouldn't involve her taking you to
去了他们的一个医疗站吧?
one of their medical stations,
-是吗 Kwon女士?   -你是怎么...
-would it now,Mrs.Kwon?  -How...
Kwon怀孕了
kwon is pregnant.
她是在这里受的孕  胎儿很健康
The fetus is healthy and was conceived on island with her husband.
他丈夫在来这之前不能生育
He was sterile before they got here.
我还在搜集其他女人的样本
I'm still working on getting samples from the other women.
应该很快能弄到Austen的
I should have Austen's soon.
有消息再联络...
I'll report back when I know more.
你从哪里弄到的?
Where'd you get that?
你去哪儿了 Jack?
Where have you been,Jack?
我问你哪儿弄来的?
I asked you where you got it.
你以为你有权利...
You really think
-来问我们吗?  -放磁带的另一面
-you're in a position to be asking us questions? -Turn the tape over.
-想都别想  -你想一把火烧死我  我就在这里!
-Stay out of it.  -You wanna burn me at stake? Here I am.
但首先你得把磁带翻过来 按下"播放"键
But first,turn the tape over. Press "play."
Juliet 我是Ben
Juliet,it's Ben.
我会派出3个小队 来带走Kwon
I'm sending three teams to extract kwon
就在后天晚上
the night after tomorrow.
没时间搜集Austen的样本了
We won't have time to run Austen's sample,
如果你确定他们怀孕了
so if you determine that she or anyone else is pregnant,
在他们的帐篷上做上标记 我们会把他们一起带走
mark their tents,and we'll take them,too.
祝你好运
Good luck.
在我们用超声波仪器的当晚
the night I saw your baby on the ultrasound,
我就告诉Jack 他们逼我这样做的
I told Jack what they were making me do.
为什么不告诉我们?
Why didn't you tell us?
因为我还不知道 该怎么做
Because I hadn't decided what to do about it yet.
"还不知道?"
"Yet?"
我想我们要忙一阵子了
I think we got some catching up to do.
妈妈?
mom?
妈妈!
我不想吓着你
Whoa,I didn't mean to scare you.
你迷路了吗  等等!
Wait,wait. Are you lost? Wait.
你是他们的人吗?
Are you one of them?
他们  谁啊?
One of who?
"敌人"
A hostile.
你还不懂那词的意思
Do you even know what that word means?
你叫什么名字?
What's your name?
Ben
能告诉我你一个人
So you wanna tell me what you're doing
在丛林当中做什么吗?
in the middle of the jungle all by yourself?
我离开了家...
I left home,and...
我来找我的妈妈
I'm looking for my mom.
你认为她在这里?
You think she's out here?
你不会相信我的
You wouldn't believe me.
说来听听
Try me.
她死了
She's dead.
在这座岛上吗?
Did she die here...on the island?
不是
No.
是在我很小的时候
When I was a baby.
你在...
Did you see her...
这里看见她了Ben 在这丛林里?
Out here,Ben,in the jungle?
她和我说话
She talked to me.
她说了什么?
What did she say?
我不能跟着她
That I couldn't come with her.
她说还不是时候
She said it wasn't time yet.
你该回家了
You should go home now.
大家都会来找你的
Your people will be looking for you.
我不想回去了!
I don't wanna go back there!
我恨那里!
I hate it there!
把我带走吧
Take me with you.
也许我能这样做...
Maybe that can happen...
如果这就是你想要的Ben
Maybe,I mean,if that's what you really want,Ben,
这是你真正想要的
if that's what you want.
我要你好好想想...
I want you to think about that...
你必须很有耐心
And you're gonna have to be very,very patient.
我们到了
We're here.
你会把手电关了的John
You'll want to turn off your flashlight,John.
为什么?
Why?
Jacob和你一样不喜欢高科技产品
Jacob feels the same way about technology as you do.
一旦打开这扇门 你就没有回头路了
Once I open this door,there's no turning back.
你确定要这样做吗?
Are you sure this is what you want?
那好吧
So be it.
Jacob...
我和John Locke在一起
I'm here with John Locke.
我们现在就进来了
We're coming in now.
Jacob...
这是John
This is John.
你不打声招呼吗 John?
Aren't you going to say hello,John?
什么?
What?
我告诉过你他不会的
I told you he wouldn't.
你在和谁说话?
Who...What are you talking about?
你看不见他吗?
You can't see him?
看见谁?
See who?
Jacob
他就坐在这个椅子上
He's sitting right here in this chair.
是的 我知道 但他坚持要这么做
Yes,i know,but he insisted.
这是什么?
What is this?
你想要知道这座岛的秘密吗?
You wanted the secrets of the island?
他们都在这里
Well,here they are.
这个人能回答每个...
This is the man who can answer every single--
不是我  是他逼我来的
I am not.He made me bring him here.
你认为这是我的...
Did you think that that was my--
-抱歉  能让我说完吗?   -你疯了
- Sorry,may I finish?  - You're crazy.
你说什么?
Excuse me?
你对这座岛一无所知对吗?
You don't know anything about the island,do you?
都是你编造出来的
You just made it all up.
-Jacob 求你了  我听不见他...     -停下
-Jacob,please,I can't hear him... - Stop.
-如果不是你说的那么响   -停下  闭嘴!
-If you're gonna talk over what he's saying   -stop.Shut up!
这是你为我准备的演出吗?
You're putting on a show for me?
还是你...
or do you...
真的认为有人在那里?
Do you really think there's someone there?
我知道有人在那里
I know there's someone there.
你什么也不知道
You don't know anything.
很抱歉你这么想 John
I'm sorry you feel that way,John,
很抱歉你的眼界太狭窄了
and I'm sorry that you're too limited to see.
你真是可悲
You're pathetic.
救救我
Help me.
你说什么?
What did you just say?
我...我什么也没说
I...I didn't say anything.
不  你说了  我听见了
Oh,yes,you did.I heard you.
你说...
You said that--
够了!
that's enough!
你玩够了!
You've had your fun!
那是什么?
What was that?
那是Jacob
That was Jacob
你听见了什么 John?
what did you hear? John
Jacob对你说了什么?
what did Jacob say to you ?
他什么也没对我说
he didn't say anything to me ,
是你说的
you did
你在说什么?
what you talking about?
根本没什么Jacob  Ben  我不会因为...
there is no Jacob   I'm not gonna be taken in
你昨晚的表演而上当的
by a little show you put on last night
你是个骗子
you're a fraud
你的人该知道真相
and this time your people will tell the truth
而且这不是我们来的路
and this is not the way we came
我带你走了另一条路
I'm taking you back another way
我想让你看样东西
I want to show you something first
我已经看够了
I'm seeing enough
John你没说错
you know John, you're not wrong
我告诉你的一些事...
some of the things I told you...
我告诉大家的一些事...
some of the things I told everybody...
都不是真的
are something not ture
比如说呢?
like what
从头说起
well,first start is
我不是出生在这座岛上的
I wasn't born on this island
那你是从哪儿来的?
where did you come from
这就是我带你去看的原因
that's what I want to show you
早上好
Morning.
等一下
Okay,wait.
就放在这里
Put it right...right down there.
又有什么事了?
What's the problem now?
早上你的话挺多的啊
You're usually chatty cathy in the morning.
今天是我生日
It's my birthday.
我不知道为什么我会傻到相信...
I don't know why I keep fooling myself into thinking
总有一天你会记得的我的生日
that one of these years you're actually gonna remember.
告诉你吧
Well,I tell you what.
我们今早要做的就是...
All we gotta do this morning is
把东西运到珍珠舱
run this stuff out to pearl station.
我们为什么不去高原
Why don't we go up to the mesa,
一起喝些啤酒呢?
drink some beers?
一起...
Have some...
我不知道...
I don't know...
父亲与儿子的事?
Father and son time?
我喜欢这样
I'd like that.
好吧
Okay.
不能说它不美啊
You sure can't say it ain't beautiful.
你怪我吗?
Do you really blame me?
什么?
What?
你真的认为她的死是我的错吗?
Do you really think it's my fault that she died?
我怎么知道?
What do I know?
干嘛一直看表?
Why do you keep looking at your watch?
有约会吗?
You got a date?
听着...
Listen...
如果能让你好受些...
If it makes you feel any better
我会尽力
I will do my best
在明年记住你的生日的
to remember your birthday next year.
我认为这不会发生了  爸爸
I don't think that's gonna happen,dad.
你什么意思?
What do yo mean?
你知道我也很想念她
You know,I've missed her,too,
也许和你一样想她
maybe as much as you have.
但区别是...
But the difference is
从我能记事起...
that for as long as I can remember,
我就必须忍受你
I've had to put up with you.
要做到这个
and doing that
必须有很大的耐心
required a tremendous amount of patience.
再见了  爸爸
Good-bye,dad.
Ben...
你想让我们去找他的尸体吗?
You want us to,uh,go get his body?
不  把他留在那儿
No,leave him out there.
好吧
ok
我就是从这里来的 John
This is where I came from,John.
这些就是我的人...
These are my people...
达摩组织
The Dharma Initiative.
他们是来寻求和平的...
They came here seeking harmony...
但他们却不能和...
But they couldn't even coexist with
当地居民共存
the island's original inhabitants.
一方必须得消失
And when it became clear that one side had to go,
一方必须得被清除
one side had to be purged...
我做了我该做的
I did what I had to do.
我是那个明智的人
I was one of the people that was smart enough to
而不像他们的结局 就是在这坑里...
make sure that I didn't end up in that ditch...
这也就是我比你聪明的原因 John
Which makes me considerably smarter than you,John.
Jacob对你说了什么?
What did Jacob say to you?
你为什么要这样做?
Why did you do this?
因为你听见他了
Because you heard him.
现在我想知道他说了什么
Now I need to know what he said.
"救救我"
Help me
John...
我不会再问你第二遍
I'm not gonna ask you again.
他和你说了什么?
What did he say to you?
他说...
He said...
"救救我"
Help me.
我真的非常希望他能救你 John
Well,I certainly hope he helps you,John.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
双语版字幕由YYeTs春天花花英语教研组制作
仅供学习交流 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎有能力的爱好者加入我们字幕组 www.YYETS.com
■